## Hi! I'm Ilaria Olimpia Posca, a front-end developer who loves = ["languages", "photography", "cultural heritage"];

Name & Surname Date of Birth Address Telephone E-Mail

Resume

Ilaria Olimpia Posca August 21st, 1986 via bari 4a- 20143 Milan, Italy +39 373 8655086 ilaria.posca@gmail.com

it.linkedin.com/in/ilariaolimpia-posca https://www.ilariaolimpiaposca.com/

Self presentation

**Portfolio** & Linkedin

I'm Ilaria a 34 years old **passionate** and **accurate** front-end developer with an eagle-eve that comes from my passion for photography. This gives me a good knowledge of all Adobe products such as Illustrator and Photoshop and also of their Gnu-alternatives.

During the last year I have worked with companies such as: Sky DE (CRM) Danone(Gallia), Limina, Acea, Alfaparf, Cariboni, Fai Service, Villa Flaminia, Generali, OZ Racing, Rheingold, Ritrama, La Roche Posay, Treccani.

Competences

Languages

- Most common web platforms such as : Adobe Experience Manager, Liferay, WordPress, Joomla, Oracle Siebel CRM, Salesforce:
- HTML & CSS (and its preprocessors/framework such as SASS, LESS, Foundation, Bootstrap)
- Vanilla Javascript (Ecmascript 5/6) and its framework: JQuery, VueJS, React(and basic concept of states management) and Angular IS (basic knowledge);
- Good knowledge in most common agile development

Jira, Confluence, BitBucket, Bamboo, Git;

- Good knowledge of Unix Systems and DOS;
- Basic PHP
- Good knowledge of tools such as task runner (Grunt), Toolkit (Gulp) and package manager (NPM, Bower, Yarn);
- Basic knowledge of deployment platforms (Docker and **Jenkins**)

Italian Mother tongue English C1

Swedish C1 Norwegian B2 French B1 Spanish Dutch A2 A2 A2 Russian

## Work experiences Current & previous

March 2021 - now Nov 2020 - Jan 2021 Jan 2020 - Aug 2020 October 2019 - Nov 2019 July 2019 - Nov 2019 October 2018 - June 2019 June 2018 - Sept. 2018	Front-End Developer at Reply-Invetsech-Blue Application Developer at Btwin-Invetsech-Blue Application Developer at Accenture - Investech-Blue Development of Oracle Siebel CRM Web-Developer at LiminaRivista - Freelance Development of a custom theme for a Web-magazine based on Wordpress Junior Front-end Developer at Accenture - Investech-Blue Development on Enterprise CMS Junior Front-end developer at Doing part of Capgemini, Milan Development of Corporate Websites Internship Front-end developer at Filmmaster's web agency Gag, Milan Custom DEM and GDPR pages
June 2012 - Sept. 2017 September 2012 - June 2014 April 2010 - Jan. 2012 November 2010 - Sept. 2011	Freelance Swedish interpreter & translator: Milan, Rotterdam, Bergamo. Mother tongue teacher at <i>Medbrogareskolan</i> , Göteborg Content Manager & Photo editor at <i>Folkuniveritetet</i> , Göteborg Awarded in 2012 as <i>Best Educational Website</i> at <i>Swedish Web Awards</i> Corporate Media Manager at <i>ClaireDK</i> , Mölndal

2009 - 2010	Photo reporter at <i>GötebrogsPosten</i> , Göteborg
September 2009	Photographer at Sound in a Frame six young talents
March 2008 - Sept. 2009	intertwined, Milan
September 2004 - June	Post-Production & Assistant at Pink Turtle, Milan
2005	Internship Digital Archivist at Fondazione A.Ratti, Como

## Education and training Schools & Diplomas

April 2020	Advanced Oracle API Javascript at Oracle University, Milan
January 2019	Adobe Experience Manager at NTT Data, Rome
March 2018 - June 2018	Front-end Developer at Manpower Formazione, Milan
anuary 2012 - June 2012	Search Engine Optimization at InfoMediaTech AB, Göteborg
September 2012 - June	Literary Composition (Litterär Gestaltning) at Folkuniversitetet
2012	Göteborg
	Thesis on: The Scandinavian Utopia (Den Skandinaviska Utopi)
September 2010 - Sept.	marks 4/5
2012	Highschool Diploma Swedish A&B at Folkuniversitetet,
	Göteborg
	Thesis on: Swedish Camera development from Early years to
	Hasselblad (Svenska kamera tillverking från hålkameror till
September 2006 - July	måne) marks 4/5
2009	Member of the Student's Council and Class President
	Bachelor Degree in <i>Photography</i> at Istituto Europeo di Design,
September 2005 - July	Milan
2006	Visual Art department marks 95/100
September 2000 - July	Philosophy at Università Statale di Milano, Milan
2005	Diploma Leonardo Project at Liceo Artistico Caravaggio, Milan
2000	Thesis on: Freud & Jung: How the advent of psychoanalysis
	changed art marks 80/100